Finding Aid for Cornelia G. Kennedy papers
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- U.S. Court of Appeals, 6th Circuit 1970-2012
  - Circuit Court Committee Files
    The subseries includes meeting material, extensive correspondence, and a newsletter for former law clerks, among other related files.
    - Committees of the Court 1986-1994 (Box 22)
    - Rules Committee
      - Procedures in Death Penalty Cases 1984 (Box 22)
      - Correspondence
        - 1981-1987 (Box 22)
        - 1988-1989 (Box 22)
        - Attorney Disciplinary/Disclosure Rules, Amendments 1989 (Box 23)
        - 1990 (Box 23)
        - 1991, 2 folders (Box 23)
        - Local Rules Project
          - Report 1991 (Box 23)
          - Background 1991 (Box 23)
        - 1992, 2 folders (Box 23)
        - 1993, 2 folders (Box 23)
        - 1994, 2 folders (Box 23)
        - 1995, 2 folders (Box 23)
        - 1996-1997 (Box 23)
        - 1998, 2 folders (Box 24)
        - 1999 (Box 24)
      - Meetings
        - November 24, 1986 Detroit, 1986-1987 (Box 24)
        - June 14, 1988 Cincinnati, 1987-1988 (Box 24)
        - February 8, 1989 Cincinnati, 1988-1989 (Box 24)
        - January 30, 1991 Cincinnati, 1988-1991 (Box 24)
    - Advisory Committee on Rules (Attorney Advisory Committee)
      - 1980-1987 (Box 24)
      - 1988-1990, 2 folders (Box 24)
      - 1991 (Box 24)
      - 1993-1994, 2 folders (Box 24)
      - 1995-1996 (Box 24)
    - Docket Control Committee 1980-1988 (Box 24)
    - Court Reporter Committee
      - 1984-1985 (Box 24)
      - 1986 (Box 24)
      - 1987-1989 (Box 24)
      - 1990-1992 (Box 24)
    - Library Committee
      - Inventories
        - 1975-1979 (Box 24)
        - 1982-1985 (Box 24)
      - News and Notes (Box 25)
        - 1979-1992, 2 folders (Box 25)
    - Investigating Committee 1988 (Box 25)
    - Space, Facilities, and Security Committee
      - Court Space 1980-1986 (Box 25)
      - Hotel Space 1981 (Box 25)
      - Detroit Court Security 1995-1997 (Box 25)
    - Ad Hoc Committee to Review the 6th Circuit Judicial Conference 1988-1989 (Box 25)
  - Sixth Circuit Judicial Council
    The subseries includes the Council meetings material and correspondence.
    - Council Members 1991-1992 (Box 25)
    - Response to Certification of Frank J. Battisti 1973, 1982-1985 (Box 25)
    - Schlachet Matter 1982-1983 (Box 25)
    - Council Committees
      - Executive Committee 1989-1990 (Box 25)
      - Standing Committee Governing Complaints of Judicial Misconduct or Disability 1990, 1992 (Box 25)
      - Juror Utilization 1981-1986 (Box 25)
      - Standards for Authorization of Temporary Personnel 1985-1986 (Box 25)
      - Sentencing Guidelines Oversight Committee 1987 (Box 25)
      - Federal-State Bar Ad Hoc Committee 1982-1989 (Box 25)
    - Council Meetings and Correspondence
      - 1980, 2 folders (Box 26)
      - 1981 (Box 26)
      - Correspondence 1983 (Box 26)
      - Meetings 1983, 3 folders (Box 26)
      - 1984, 4 folders (Box 26)
      - 1985, 4 folders (Box 27)
      - 1985-1986 (Box 27)
      - 1987-1988 (Box 27)
      - 1989-1990, 2 folders (Box 27)
      - 1991-1992 (Box 27)
      - 1994, 2 folders (Box 27)
      - Minutes 1997, 1998, 2001 (Box 27)
    - Chambers Newsletter 1991-2011 (Box 27)
  - Correspondence
    The subseries contains general and professional correspondence, as well as invitations and congratulations notes from colleagues.
    - Judicial 1987-1993, 4 folders (Box 27)
    - General and Miscellaneous
      - 1979-1980, 2 folders (Box 27)
      - 1981-1982, 4 folders (Box 27)
      - 1983-1984, 2 folders (Box 28)
      - 1985-1987, 6 folders (Box 28)
      - 1988-1989, 3 folders (Box 28)
      - 1990-1992, 8 folders (Box 28)
    - Hanssen, Henry R. 1981 (Box 29)
    - Herrington, Marion 1981-1982 (Box 29)
    - Invitations 1979-1986, 3 folders (Box 29)
    - Congratulations 1980-1989, 2 folders (Box 29)
  - Published Opinions
    The Published Opinions subseries contains volumes with opinions dated between 1979 and 2006.
    - Volumes 1-3 1979-1980, 1981, 1982, 3 three-ring binders (Box 29)
    - Volumes 4-8 and 10 1983-1987, 1989, 6 three-ring binders (Box 30)
    - 2001-2002, 2003-2004, 2005-2006, 3 bound, hardcover volumes (Box 30)
  - Court Cases
    The subseries contains a selection of Kennedy's court case files.
    - 77-1546 to 79-5441 1980-1981, 21 folders (Box 43)
    - 80-1535 to 81-1485 1981-1983, 23 folders (Box 44)
    - 81-1472 to 81-5186 1982-1984, 23 folders (Box 45)
    - 81-5386 to 82-1677 1982-1985, 17 folders (Box 46)
    - 82-1772 to 82-5020 1982-1986, 22 folders (Box 47)
    - 82-5140 to 83-5533 1982-1985, 23 folders (Box 48)
    - 83-5168 to 84-1288 1983-1987, 14 folders (Box 49)
    - 84-1296 to 84-3514 1984-1989, 18 folders (Box 50)
    - 84-3546 to 84-5276 1984-1988, 13 folders (Box 51)
    - 84-5518 to 85-1762 1985-1987, 20 folders (Box 52)
    - 85-1880 to 85-3959 1986-1994, 17 folders (Box 53)
    - 85-3975 to 86-1017 1986-1989, 21 folders (Box 54)
    - 86-1249 to 86-3214 1987-1989, 18 folders (Box 55)
    - 86-3413 to 87-5024 1987-1989, 14 folders (Box 56)
    - 87-1070 to 87-5897 1987-1990, 20 folders (Box 57)
    - 88-1284 to 89-5107 1988-1991, 14 folders (Box 58)
    - 89-2364 to 90-3990 1989-1991, 18 folders (Box 59)
    - 90-4028 to 92-6159 1990-1994, 18 folders (Box 60)
    - 93-1456 to 95-1560 1993-1997, 18 folders (Box 61)
    - 95-1686 to 97-2140 1996-1999, 20 folders (Box 62)
    - 97-2312 to 99-6565 1998-2001, 22 folders (Box 63)
    - 00-2103 to 04-1207 2001-2005, 24 folders (Box 64)
    - 04-3672 to 09-5120 2005-2011, 18 folders (Box 65)
- Judicial Conference of the United States 1970-1997
  The Judicial Conference of the United States series (8 linear feet, 1970-1997), is divided into seven subseries that follow the Conference's changing structure overtime: Advisory Committee on Judicial Activities, 1970-1979; Joint Committee on the Code of Judicial Conduct, 1973-1979; Advisory/Joint Committees, 1973-1979; Ethics Advisory Panel/Judicial Ethics Committee, 1979-1981; Advisory Committee on Codes of Conduct, 1980-1986; Committee to Review Circuit Council and Disability Orders; and Other Committees and Judicial Activities. The Judicial Conference of the United States series as a whole reflects the history of some key committees of the Conference and presents a fairly complete representation of the inquiries concerning ethical questions that were considered by the Judicial Conference during the years referenced. Material in the subseries includes meeting agenda, correspondence and memoranda, reports, and the contents of Dockets. The Docket numbers were assigned to the inquiries submitted to the committees in the order they were received so topics can range widely from one docket to the next. Some general themes include recusal or disqualification, family matters, the effect of non-judicial activities on public image, and conflicts of interest. For example, inquiries from Judge John J. Sirica during 1973-1975 (e.g., Docket #62) reflected public concerns after the Watergate break-in. Other advisory opinions concern hospital boards (Docket #1), condominium boards (Docket #2), non-reporting judges (Docket #3), family corporations (Docket #4), federal funds solicited and used (Docket #5), and community water systems (Docket #6). Additionally represented are dockets regarding the propriety of a judge serving on the Advisory Policy Board of the National Crime Information Center (Docket #35), the advertising and promotion of judicial writings of U.S. Judges (Docket #110), a part-time magistrate (Docket #188), disqualification and participation in non-judicial activities (Docket #192), and an article in the Legal Times of Washington (Docket #207). Advisory opinions issued specifically by the Advisory Committee on Codes of Conduct include dockets regarding a spouse's ownership of stock/antitrust class action (Docket #291), and senior judges serving as arbitrators (Docket #322).
  - Advisory Committee on Judicial Activities 1970-1979
    - Resource Material on Federal Ethical Considerations 1970-1973 (Box 31)
    - General Correspondence and Meeting Agenda
      - 1973-1979, 5 folders (Box 31)
      - Part-Time Referee/Magistrate 1973-1974 (Box 31)
      - Opinion Review, Docket No. 192 Disqualification and Participation in Non-Judicial Activities 1978-1979 (Box 31)
      - Legislation: Ethics in Government Act 1978 (Box 31)
      - Semi-Annual Meetings and Agenda
        - Marco Island, Florida January 29-30, 1975 (Box 31)
        - Hilton Head, South Carolina August 13-14, 1975 (Box 31)
        - Tucson, Arizona January 28-29, 1976 (Box 31)
        - Jackson Hole, Wyoming July 28-29, 1976 (Box 31)
        - Key Biscayne, Florida, Agenda Item II-Other Matters February, 1977 (Box 31)
        - Williamsburg, Virginia, Agenda July 27-28, 1977 (Box 31)
  - Joint Committee on the Code of Judicial Conduct 1973-1979
    - General Correspondence and Meeting Agenda
      - 1974-1979, 5 folders (Box 31)
      - Report of the Review Committee to the Judicial Conference, for the reporting period January 1 to June 30, 1975 (Box 31)
      - Report of the Review Committee to the Judicial Conference, on Extra-Judicial Income, filed for July 1-December 31, 1977 (Box 31)
      - Marco Island Meeting January 31, 1975 (Box 31)
      - Hilton Head Meeting August 15, 1975, 15 folders (Box 31)
      - Tucson Meeting, January 30, 1976 (Box 31)
  - Advisory/Joint Committees 1973-1979
    - General Correspondence and Meeting Agenda
      - Miami, Florida, January 30-31-February 1 1978
        - Advisory Committee Agenda 1978 (Box 31)
        - Federal Judicial Center Handbook on Disqualification 1977 (Box 31)
      - Denver, Colorado July 26-28, 1978 (Box 31)
      - Palm Beach Shores, Florida January 24-26, 1979 (Box 31)
    - Advisory Opinions (Inquiries) 1973-1979
      - Dockets No. 1-5 1973-1974, 5 folders (Box 31)
      - Dockets No. 6-100 1973-1975, 87 folders (Box 32)
      - Dockets No. 101-105, 1976-1978, 80 folders (Box 33)
      - Dockets No. 181-207 1978-1979, 28 folders (Box 34)
  - Ethics Advisory Panel/Judicial Ethics Committee 1979-1981
    - General Correspondence and Meeting Agenda
      - General Correspondence 1979 (Box 34)
      - Meeting, Lake Park, Florida January 1980, 1979-1980
        - Proposed Agenda 1979-1980 (Box 34)
        - Agenda Items 1-4 1980 (Box 34)
        - Agenda Items 5-7 1980 (Box 34)
        - Agenda Items 8-12 1980 (Box 34)
      - General Correspondence 1980 (Box 34)
      - Amendments to Canons 4-C and 2 1978-1980, 2 folders (Box 34)
      - Special Material 1980 (Box 34)
    - Advisory Panel on Financial Disclosure Reports, Inquiries No. 79-1 through 79-15 1979 (Box 34)
    - Ethics Advisory Panel, Inquiries No. 79-16, 18, 22, 24, 25, 27, 29, 33, 37, 38, 39 1979, 11 folders (Box 34)
    - Ethics Advisory Committee, Inquiries No. 31 and 35 1979 (Box 34)
    - Advisory Panel on Financial Disclosure Reports and Judicial Activities, Inquiry No. 41 1979 (Box 34)
    - Advisory Opinions (Inquiries) 1979-1981
      - Dockets No. 208-213 June 1979, 6 folders (Box 34)
      - Dockets No. 214-216 1979-1981, 3 folders (Box 34)
      - Docket No. 217, Judge Samuel Conti Invited Article, "generally opposed to the use of juries in complex civil antitrust cases," i.e., "complex cases like Memorex v. IBM," 1979 (Box 34)
      - Dockets No. 218-224 1979, 7 folders (Box 34)
      - Dockets No. 225-230 1979, 6 folders (Box 34)
      - Dockets No. 231-240 1979, 10 folders (Box 34)
      - Dockets No. 241-245 and 247 1980, 6 folders (Box 35)
      - Docket No. 248, Foundation Board Membership 1980-1981 (Box 35)
      - Dockets No. 249-250 1980, 2 folders (Box 35)
      - Dockets No. 251-254 March 1980, 4 folders (Box 35)
  - Advisory Committee on Codes of Conduct 1980-1986
    - General Correspondence and Meeting Agenda
      - Club Membership Correspondence 1979-1984 (Box 35)
      - Comment Sheet on Club Membership 1980-1981 (Box 35)
      - Educational Programs for Federal Judges
        - Law and Economics Institutes 1979-1980 (Box 35)
        - Guidelines for Judicial Participation 1980 (Box 35)
      - Code and Director of Administrative Office 1982 (Box 35)
      - Code and Federal Defenders, Circuit Executives, Staff Attorneys 1979, 1985 (Box 35)
      - General Correspondence 1981-1986 (Box 35)
      - Meeting Correspondence and Agenda Planning
        - Delavan, Wisconsin, Summer 1980 (Box 35)
        - Vail, Colorado, Summer 1981 (Box 35)
        - Big Sky, Montana, Summer 1982 (Box 35)
        - West Palm Beach, Florida, Winter 1983 (Box 35)
        - San Diego, California, Summer 1983 (Box 35)
        - West Palm Beach, Florida, Winter 1984 (Box 35)
        - Carmel, California, Summer 1984 (Box 35)
        - West Palm Beach, Florida, Winter 1985 (Box 35)
        - Mackinac Island, Michigan, Summer 1985 (Box 35)
        - Rancho Santa Fe, California, Winter 1986 (Box 35)
    - Reports to the Chief Justice 1979-1985 (Box 35)
    - Telephone Inquiries 1980-1985 (Box 35)
    - Published Advisory Opinions 1981-1985
      - No. 17, Travel and Hotel Expenses-Judges and Wives 1984 (Box 35)
      - No. 53, Political Activity of Spouse 1981-1982 (Box 35)
      - No. 63, Disqualification re Amici 1980-1981 (Box 35)
      - No. 68, Disqualification in Class Actions 1981 (Box 35)
      - No. 70, Resigned Judges Appearing as Counsel 1985-1986 (Box 35)
      - No. 73, Requests for Letters of Recommendation/Endorsements 1982-1983 (Box 35)
      - No. 74, Disqualification-Law Clerk's Future Employer 1984 (Box 35)
      - No. 75, Military and Other Governmental Pension 1984 (Box 35)
      - No. 76, Service of State Employees as Part-Time Magistrates 1985 (Box 35)
      - No. 77, Disqualification when Judge's Relative is Spouse of Law Firm Partner 1985 (Box 35)
      - No. 78, Disqualification when Judge is Utility Ratepayer or Taxpayer 1985 (Box 35)
      - Bankruptcy Judges (publication postponed) 1985 (Box 35)
    - Advisory Opinions (Inquiries) 1980-1985
      - Dockets No. 255-275 1980-1983 (20) (Box 35)
      - Dockets No. 276-370 1980-1985, 95 folders (Box 36)
      - Dockets No. 371-477 1983-1985, 115 folders (Box 37)
  - Committee on Codes of Conduct, Final Proposed Revisions 1992
    - Comments on Proposed Changes to Rules of Civil Procedure 1989, 1993 (Box 37)
    - Comments on Proposed Amendments to Rules of Appellate Procedure 1994-1995 (Box 37)
    - Preliminary Draft of Proposed Revision of the Federal Rules of Appellate Procedure 1996 (Box 37)
    - Comments on Proposed Style Revision of the Appellate Rules 1997 (Box 37)
    - Comments on Proposed Amendments to Rules of Criminal Procedure 1997-1998 (Box 37)
  - Committee to Review Circuit Council Conduct and Disability Orders 1980-1997
    - Judicial Conduct and Disability Orders 1982-1993 (Box 38)
    - Recommendations of the National Commission on Judicial Discipline and Removal 1993-1994 (Box 38)
    - General Correspondence and Meetings
      - 1993 (Box 38)
      - January-May, 1994 (Box 38)
      - June-August, 1994 (Box 38)
      - September-December, 1994 (Box 38)
      - 1995 (Box 38)
      - 1996 (Box 38)
      - Meeting, New Orleans 1996 (Box 38)
      - 1996-1997 (Box 38)
      - Other Memoranda, Administrative Office of the U.S. Courts 1991, 1995 (Box 38)
    - Background Materials
      - Public Opinion 1994-1996 (Box 38)
      - Federal Legislation 1980-1990 (Box 38)
    - Petitions for Review 1995-1997, 3 folders (Box 38)
  - Other Committees and Judicial Activities 1978-1994
    - Ad Hoc Committee on Cameras in the Courtroom 1981-1984 (Box 38)
    - General Correspondence and Meetings. Washington, D.C. March, 1978 (Box 38)
    - Committee on Judicial Ethics 1988 (Box 38)
    - Committee to Study the Judicial Conference 1987 (Box 38)
    - Committee on Long Range Planning, Proposed Long Range Plan for the Federal Courts, 1994 (Box 38)
- Federal Judicial Center (FJC) 1971-1999
  The Federal Judicial Center (FJC) series (1 linear foot, 1971-1999), contains correspondence, rosters, and other materials related to Judge Kennedy's term as a board member of the Center. The series also includes examples of public education materials about the judicial branch of government and educational programs for judges, notably from the Judicial Fellows Program (a program jointly sponsored by the U.S. Supreme Court, the FJC, and the Administrative Office of the U.S. Courts).
  - Bicentennial of the Judiciary Act of 1789
    - Public Education Materials 1988-1989 (Box 39)
    - National Conference of Federal Appellate Judges 1988 (Box 39)
  - "Conduct of the Voir Dire Examination: Practices and Opinions of Federal Judges," 1977 (Box 39)
  - Conference of Metropolitan District Chief Judges 1977-1979, 8 folders (Box 39)
  - Operation of the Federal Judicial Councils 1978-1979 (Box 39)
  - Board Member Correspondence and Meetings
    - Board Rosters 1981-1985 (Box 39)
    - Automated Data Processing and Courts Administration 1981-1983 (Box 39)
    - Board Membership and Agenda for Washington, DC Meeting 1983 (Box 39)
    - Williamsburg, VA and Washington, DC Meetings 1984, 2 folders (Box 39)
    - Final Year of Non-Renewable Term 1984-1985 (Box 39)
  - Interview for The Third Branch, Bulletin of the Federal Courts, 1984 (Box 39)
  - Judicial Fellows Program (Jointly Sponsored by Supreme Court, FJC, and Administrative Office of the U.S. Courts)
    - Judicial Fellows Commissions
      - Supreme Court of the U.S.
        - 1982-1985, 2 folders (Box 39)
        - 1986 (Box 39)
        - 1987 (Box 39)
      - 1988-1994, 4 folders (Box 39)
    - New District Judge (Personal, with Sentencing) 1971, 2 folders (Box 39)
    - Court's Role in Desegregation of Education Litigation 1975 (Box 39)
  - Continuing Education Seminars for Federal Judges
    - Newly Appointed District Judges
      - 1977-1978, 2 folders (Box 39)
      - 1979-1980, 3 folders (Box 39)
    - Newly Appointed Appellate Judges 1983-1985 (Box 39)
  - Workshops for Circuit Judges
    - 1983-1985, 3 folders (Box 39)
    - 1990 1996, 2 folders (Box 39)
    - 2001 (Box 39)
  - Antitrust Seminar, University of Michigan 1981 (Box 39)
  - Harvard Law School Summer Program of Instruction for Lawyers (with financial support from FJC) 1989 (Box 39)
  - Report of the 9th Circuit Gender-Race Bias Study Task Force of 1993, 1992-1994 (Box 39)
  - Sentencing Institute, 4th and 6th Circuits 1993 (Box 39)
  - Diversity Training Workshop for Women Judges 1994 (Box 39)
  - University of Notre Dame Workshop on "The Craft of Judging," 1999 (Box 39)
  - National Symposium for Court of Appeals Judges, Washington, D.C. November 3-4, 2005 (Box 39)
- American Bar Association 1971-1989
  The American Bar Association (ABA) series (1 linear feet, 1971-1989), includes some materials related to a centennial annual meeting in 1978 and correspondence regarding production of a videocassette featuring Judge Kennedy on appellate advocacy. The bulk of the series represents Judge Kennedy's committee service work in the Judicial Administration Division of the ABA.
  - Centennial Annual Meeting, New York 1978 (Box 40)
  - Videotape Program on Appellate Advocacy, Washington, DC 1980 (Box 40)
  - Special Committee on Coordination of Federal Judicial Improvements 1983 (Box 40)
  - Judges' Advisory Committee to the Standing Committee on Ethics and Professional Responsibility
    - Part 1 1984-1986 (Box 40)
    - Part 2 1987-1989 (Box 40)
  - Fellows of the American Bar Foundation 1971-1981 (Box 40)
  - General and Miscellaneous 1973-1987 (Box 40)
  - Judicial Administration Division
    - General Correspondence 1975-1976 (Box 40)
    - Committee on Budget and Finance/Continuing Budget 1975-1976 (Box 40)
    - National Conference of Federal Trial Judges
      - General Correspondence
        - 1972-1973 (Box 40)
        - 1973-1974 (Box 40)
        - 1974-1975 (Box 40)
        - 1975-1976, 2 folders (Box 40)
        - 1976-1978 (Box 40)
      - Meetings
        - 1972-1973 (Box 40)
        - 1974-1975, 3 folders (Box 40)
      - Nominating Committee 1972, 1976-1978 (Box 40)
      - Committee for Liaison with District Judges Association 1974-1975 (Box 40)
      - Public Education Committee 1974-1975 (Box 40)
      - Executive Committee
        - Resolution-Chief Justice and Court of Claims Judges--Special Admission of Lawyers 1975 (Box 40)
        - Article by Frank Battisti, "An Independent Judiciary or..." included with Correspondence from Orrin G. Judd 1975 (Box 40)
      - State and Federal Court Relations Committee 1977 (Box 40)
    - Committee on Courts and the Community 1980-1981 (Box 40)
    - Membership Committee 1981-1983, 2 folders (Box 40)
    - Appellate Judges' Conference
      - Executive Committee 1981-1985, 3 folders (Box 40)
      - Long Range Planning Committee
        - 1982-1983 (Box 40)
        - 1984 (Box 40)
        - 1985 (Box 40)
      - General Correspondence 1984-1985 (Box 40)
- Other Professional Organizations and Meetings 1968-2009
  The final series, Other Professional Organizations and Meetings (2 linear feet, 1968-2009), includes materials such as meeting agenda and program notes that represent Judge Kennedy's other professional memberships and activities, as well as her participation in some civic organizations and women's events. U.S. Department of Justice continuing education programs for judges, and moot court competitions at law schools for students of the law are also represented.
  - National College of State Trial Judges
    - Participants' List 1968 (Box 41)
    - General Correspondence
      - 1968-1969 (Box 41)
      - 1970 1972 (Box 41)
  - Federal Bar Association
    - Detroit Chapter, General Correspondence
      - 1971-1978 (Box 41)
      - 1980-1982 (Box 41)
      - 1986-1988 (Box 41)
      - 1989-1993 (Box 41)
    - Nashville Chapter, Appellate Practice Seminar 1985 (Box 41)
    - National 1979, 1985, 1998 (Box 41)
  - District Judges' Association 1978-1979 (Box 41)
  - Detroit Bar Association 1979-1994 (Box 41)
  - State Bar of Michigan
    - General Correspondence
      - 1970-1979 (Box 41)
      - 1982-1990, 4 folders (Box 41)
      - 1992-1993 (Box 41)
    - Champions of Justice Award 1994 (Box 41)
    - 50 year Honorees 1995, 1997 (Box 41)
    - Negligence Law Section Council 2006-2009 (Box 41)
  - National Commission on the Observance of International Women's Year, Historic Houston, Texas, Conference November, 1977 (Box 41)
  - National Organization for Women, Metropolitan Detroit Chapter, Women's Equality Day Program Guest Speaker 1979 (Box 41)
  - Symposium on Women in the American Judiciary, including photograph with Justice O'Connor and a journal article, National Center for State Courts with the William Bingham Foundation and the Johnson Foundation 1980-1982 (Box 41)
  - Women Lawyers Association of Michigan, 75th Anniversary Annual Meeting 1994 (Box 41)
  - Kentucky Bar Association Annual Convention, Continuing Legal Education Program, "The Women Lawyers Club," 2008 (Box 41)
  - National Association of Women Judges (NAWJ)
    - First Meeting, West Los Angeles, California October, 1979, 2 folders
      - California Women Lawyers Judges Committee (Box 41)
      - General Correspondence (Box 41)
    - Washington, D.C. Meeting and Photographs October, 1980 (Box 41)
    - Financial Report 1980-1981 (Box 41)
    - Women Lawyers Association of Michigan, Long Range Planning Committee 1984-1985 (Box 41)
    - Bicentennial Committee 1986, 1988 (Box 41)
    - Washington, D.C. Meeting 1989 (Box 41)
    - General Correspondence
      - 1989-1993, 3 folders (Box 41)
      - 1994-1997, 2002 (Box 41)
    - Women Judges' Fund for Justice
      - Background 1982-1988 (Box 41)
      - General Correspondence 1989-1990, 2 folders (Box 41)
      - General Correspondence 1991-1994, 3 folders (Box 42)
  - Moot Court Competitions at Law Schools